Guide to the Mike Cox Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2007-008
  - "Photographic equipment" – notes, correspondence, receipts, manuals and newspaper clippings, all concerning cameras and related equipment (Box 808, Folder 30)
  - "Media bibliography" – newspaper clippings on the media and "spin" (Box 809, Folder 1)
  - "Spokespersons II" – newspaper clippings on press secretaries, and the March 8, 1998 issue of The Washington Post Magazine (Box 809, Folder 2)
  - "Land ms. MLC" – edited version of text for land office map book along with editor's report by Roger Griffen, 1986 (Box 809, Folder 3)
  - "Artists, Texas and Texas Art" – numerous newspaper clippings, photos and other promotional material related to artists, with notes and drafts (Box 809, Folder 4)
  - "Adam Michael" – newspaper clippings about author, and a draft by Cox on Adams, February 1, 1983 (Box 809, Folder 5)
  - "Adams, Ramon" – article by Jeff Dykes titled The Western Worlds of Ramon Adams (Box 809, Folder 6)
  - "TX Book Festival 1998" – material relating to the book festival and Cox's attendance as author and moderator (Box 809, Folder 7)
  - "Texas Book Festival", 1997-1998 (Box 809, Folder 8)
  - "Caro, Robert II" – newspaper clippings mainly on Caro's biography of LBJ, and notes and drafts from Cox's review of the book (Box 809, Folder 9)
  - "Cokesbury Books" – two Cokesbury Book Store catalogs, newspaper clippings on the store, and notes and drafts by Cox (Box 809, Folder 10)
  - "Cox, Mike misc. mss. & proofs" – drafts by Cox, newspaper clipping of Cox's article from June 12, 1966 in the El Paso Times Sunday Magazine (Box 809, Folder 11)
  - "Crime Books" – newspaper clippings on crime books, book announcements, and an essay by Mike Kingston titled A History of the Mystery (Box 809, Folder 12)
  - "Hondo Crouch" – newspaper clippings on man known as the "clown prince of Luckenbach", some notes, and a book announcement for Hondo My Father by Becky Crouch Patterson (Box 809, Folder 13)
  - "Connie Hager" – correspondence, photos, and draft titled Connie Hager – Bird Woman by L. A. Wilke (Box 809, Folder 14)
  - "Hand book of Texas entries" – newsletters from the Handbook of Texas, newspaper clippings, and notes and drafts of biographical entries (Box 809, Folder 15)
  - "John Holmes" – newspaper clippings on Holmes' A Portrait of Texas book (Box 809, Folder 16)
  - "How to write for money" – work books for sessions one, two, four, five, seven, and eight (Box 809, Folder 17)
  - "Col. Chase Askins" – article by L. A. Wilke along with twelve black and white photos and negatives (Box 809, Folder 18)
  - "Bosworth, Allan" – correspondence and information on Bosworth (Box 809, Folder 19)
  - "Bugbee, Harold" – articles about Bugbee's work (Box 809, Folder 20)
  - "Carpenter, Liz" – one black and white photo of Carpenter with a small scratch, notes, and correspondence (Box 809, Folder 21)
  - "Mike Cochran" – book jacket from Deliver Us From Evil by Cochran, book announcement, and one black and white photo of Cochran (Box 809, Folder 22)
  - "Cramer, T. Dudley" – correspondence (Box 809, Folder 23)
  - "Dewlen, Al" – newspaper clippings about Dewlen's books, notes, and book announcements (Box 809, Folder 24)
  - "Dixon, Samuel Houston" – printout from The Handbook of Texas about Houston (Box 809, Folder 25)
  - "Document declassification" – title of article by Cox, drafts, notes, and an article from Texas A and M's Office of Public Information (Box 809, Folder 26)
  - "Duncan and Gladstone Publishers" – book announcement and review of Enchanted Rock (Box 809, Folder 27)
  - "Essay books" – article reviewing Lost in West Texas and book announcement for Commonplace Mysteries (Box 809, Folder 28)
  - "Ethnic histories" – book announcement, newspaper clippings, correspondence and The Medallion newsletter from the Texas Historical Commission, February-March 1992 (Box 809, Folder 29)
  - "John Henry Faulk II" – newspaper clippings on the life, work and death of Faulk and includes a program from his memorial service (Box 809, Folder 30)
  - "Friedman, Kinky II" – newspaper clippings about Friedman, reviews of his books, and his run for governor, 2006 (Box 809, Folder 31)
  - "Francis Fugate, El Paso" – article by Fugate and correspondence (Box 809, Folder 32)
  - "Goddard, Ruth 472-8896" – article about Goddard, and promotional material, including her photo, for her book titled Porfirio Salinas (Box 809, Folder 33)
  - "Frank Goodwyn" – correspondence between Cox and Goodwyn, and newspaper clipping of Cox review of Goodwyn's book about the King Ranch (Box 809, Folder 34)
  - "Haley, James L." – newspaper clippings, notes and draft about Haley's book Passionate Nation (Box 809, Folder 35)
  - "Media Relations – old material" – syllabus for DPS presentation of policies, material from criminal justice class and newspaper clippings relating to press matters (Box 809, Folder 36)
  - "Larry Hodge Stories" – correspondence between Cox and Hodge, notes, and Honeyholes for Panhandle Pheasants (Box 809, Folder 37)
  - "Huson, Hobart" – correspondence from Kathleen Huson Maxwell, seven photos, and newspaper clipping on Hobart (Box 809, Folder 38)
  - "Jackson, Jack" – newspaper clippings about the life, work, and death of Jackson including a piece by Jesse Sublett (Box 809, Folder 39)
  - "Media Relations issues /new" – numerous newspaper clippings on the press, media relations, and crime reporting (Box 810, Folder 1)
  - "News media issues/press law" – newspaper clippings and newsletters from F.O.I, The Freedom of Information Foundation of Texas (Box 810, Folder 2)
  - "Hangar Talk" – correspondence between Betty Cox and Bob Jamison, draft of Hangar Talk, and photocopies of various articles from the 1940's (Box 810, Folder 3)
  - "Media Relations handbook" – various handbooks about public relations, the media, and publicity (Box 810, Folder 4)
  - "Herman" – correspondence between Betty Cox and Bob Jamison and drafts of Herman (Box 810, Folder 5)
  - "Hungary" – correspondence between Betty Cox and Bob Jamison, notes, and drafts with revisions of Hungary for Pheasant" (Box 810, Folder 6)
  - "Jamison - Publications" – a few photocopies of articles written by Bob Jamison" (Box 810, Folder 7)
  - "Morgan" – correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison relating to Jamison's book and Morgan Publishing (Box 810, Folder 8)
  - "Razor-Tooth & Rattler" – essays on fax paper (Box 810, Folder 9)
  - "Razor-Tooth & Rattler" – drafts, notes, printouts from The Handbook of Texas online, and correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison (Box 810, Folder 10)
  - "Recipes" – recipes, such as Gator Sauce and Squirrel, for inclusion in Jamison's book and limited correspondence relating to the recipes (Box 810, Folder 11)
  - "Astronauts" – newspaper clippings, correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison and a 1999 community guide to Claremont, Oklahoma (Box 810, Folder 12)
  - "Banker" – magazine BANK from October 1998 and Independent Bankers from June and October 1998 (Box 810, Folder 13)
  - "Banker" – newspaper clippings on a variety of topics, correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison, one diskette, drafts and notes, and the August 2, 1999 issue of Time Magazine featuring the death of John Kennedy (Box 810, Folder 14)
  - "Amazon" – notes, drafts, and correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison (Box 810, Folder 15)
  - "Aircraft" – notes and correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison (Box 810, Folder 16)
  - "Ref. request" – correspondence, notes, and drafts from Jamison (Box 810, Folder 17)
  - "Jamison Photos" – seventeen photos including trip to the Amazon and other hunting and fishing photos (Box 810, Folder 18)
  - "Illustrations" – correspondence, two photos, and photocopies of locations with hand written notes (Box 810, Folder 19)
  - Untitled folder – materials relating to Jamison's book Airplanes, Alligators and Hi-fin Blues, nine photos, notes, and correspondence (Box 810, Folder 20)
  - "King, Larry" – newspaper clippings, two press photos of King, and book announcements (Box 810, Folder 21)
  - "John S. Mayfield" – notes and information about the Mayfield library and a Christmas card signed by Mayfield (Box 810, Folder 22)
  - "Florida Roberts" – seven photos, a booklet The True Story of the Tree, and drafts of The Stubborn Fisherman by L. A. Wilke (Box 810, Folder 23)
  - "Marshall, Bruce" – promotional material for Marshall's book Uniforms of the Alamo (Box 810, Folder 24)
  - "Katherine Anne Porter" – newspaper clippings about Porter and her childhood house in Kyle (Box 810, Folder 25)
  - "Pulp writers" – newspaper clippings on authors (Box 810, Folder 26)
  - "Readers/Writers Roundtable Solado" – list of readers and writers attended the roundtable where Mike Cox was the emcee, and photocopies of biographies, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 27)
  - "Reid, Ace" – newspaper clippings and promotional material for Cowpokes (Box 810, Folder 28)
  - "Tom Lea" – newspaper clippings about Lea and his work, and promotional material for The Brave Bulls and other works (Box 810, Folder 29)
  - "Bess Whitehead Scott" – newspaper clippings about the 100th birthday for Scott, one of Texas first women reporters (Box 810, Folder 30)
  - "Sigma Delta Chi VF#3-29" – March 1955 roster of Sigma Delta Chi, and Cox's pledge nametag (Box 810, Folder 31)
  - "Weems, Eddie" – correspondence between Cox and Weems; information on the Texas Folklore Society and the Texas Institute of Letters, and newspaper clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 810, Folder 32)
  - "Media Relations ethics" – newspaper clippings on crime and reporting (Box 811, Folder 1)
  - "Media Relations legal issues 1999" – notes and newspaper clippings (Box 811, Folder 2)
  - "BTB II proofs & letters [more Basic Texas Books]" – notes, correspondence, drafts, and galley proofs for Cox's More Basic Texas Books book (Box 811, Folder 3)
  - "They Call'em Snake Hunters MLC ms." – drafts of work by Cox (Box 811, Folder 4)
  - "Lammert History Series" – correspondence between Cox and Lammert on book proposal (Box 811, Folder 5)
  - "Guide to the Texas Revolution" – article by Cox (Box 811, Folder 6)
  - "Media Relations" – numerous newspaper clippings about the media, more FOI Focus newsletters, the 1985-86 Journalism & Ethics report, and the 1985-86 Freedom of Information report (Box 811, Folder 7)
  - "Will the dogs" – draft of story from Jamison's Airplanes, Alligators, and Hi-fin Blues (Box 811, Folder 8)
  - "Recipes" – recipes and correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison (Box 811, Folder 9)
  - "Ref. Requests" – requests from Betty Cox to confirm information for Jamison's book (Box 811, Folder 10)
  - "Doctors" – draft of The Doctors (Box 811, Folder 11)
  - "Volunteers" – information and newspaper clippings on Dayton volunteer firefighters, and correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison (Box 811, Folder 12)
  - "Mrs. Palmer Smith Elgin, Tx" – correspondence between Cox and Smith, 1990s (Box 811, Folder 13)
  - Sonnichsen, C. L." – newspaper clippings about the author/historian (Box 811, Folder 14)
  - "Floyd V. Studer indexed" – newspaper clippings on the Dean of Archeology (Box 811, Folder 15)
  - "Texas History Movies" – newspaper clippings and correspondence on re-print of book by the same title (Box 811, Folder 16)
  - "Texas Magazines" – newspaper clippings about Texas Monthly, SW Review, and the Texas Observer (Box 811, Folder 17)
  - "Travis Co. Collection" – newspaper clippings and information from the Austin History Center (Box 811, Folder 18)
  - "Cadwallader Washburn indexed" – correspondence between Cox and Mrs. Washburn from 1981, and newspaper clippings relating to draft by Washburn (Box 811, Folder 19)
  - "Bill Wittliff" – newspaper clippings about Bill Wittliff and Encino Press (Box 811, Folder 20)
  - "Media Relations- new" – numerous newspaper clippings (Box 811, Folder 21)
  - "Bibliography" – list of books with call numbers to be checked out (Box 811, Folder 22)
  - "Birds" – photocopies of information about birds and correspondence between Betty Cox and Jameson (Box 811, Folder 23)
  - "Characters" – correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison, notes, and photocopies of various newspaper clippings (Box 811, Folder 24)
  - "Belize" – notes, drafts with revisions, and correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison, information on bats, information on Belize, and drafts of Jamison's Land of the Jaguars (Box 811, Folder 25)
  - "Dogs" – a faxed copied Dogs (Box 811, Folder 26)
  - "Family" – notes, photocopies of newspaper clippings, and correspondence (Box 811, Folder 27)
  - "Bear Hunt" – correspondence, drafts of bear story by Jamison, and information on bears (Box 811, Folder 28)
  - "Gators" – numerous newspaper clippings, information on alligators and crocodiles, correspondence between Betty Cox and Jamison, drafts of Alligator Hunt II and Alligator on My Hook by Jamison (Box 811, Folder 29)
  - "Women Writers/TX" – newspaper clippings on female authors (Box 811, Folder 30)
  - "A. C. Greene" – newspaper clippings, a photo of Greene, and book announcements (Box 811, Folder 31)
  - "Jamison – NASA" – material from the LBJ Space Center including a color print of the crew of the eighth manned Apollo mission (Box 811, Folder 32)
  - "Authors, Texas indexed" – photos, newspaper clippings on authors, book announcements, and program from the Texas Writers Roundup, 1970-1971 (Box 812, Folder 1)
  - "Book Club of Texas" – newspaper clippings, booklets, and programs from meetings (Box 812, Folder 2)
  - "Eakin Ranger book" – correspondence between Cox and Eakin Press, notes, newspaper clippings with review of Cox's book about the Texas Rangers, glossary of terms, and Eakin Press catalogs (Box 812, Folder 3)
  - "E books/ promotion 2000" – newspaper clippings on e-book publishing and online book stores, and a newspaper clipping on the latest Harry Potter movie (Box 812, Folder 4)
  - "Austin: Books about" – newspaper clippings, notes, and book announcements (Box 812, Folder 5)
  - "Writers, Texas/Deceased" – numerous newspaper clippings, book announcements, Cox's draft of piece on H. B. Fox, and photocopied material from the following books: Pen Points by Henry Harrison, Deep in the Hearts of Texans by Perry Wampler Nichols, and The Gay Place by William Brammer (Box 812, Folder 6)
  - "The Printing Salesman's Herald" – books 39, 31, 44, 41 and 40 by the same title, published by Champion Papers (Box 812, Folder 7)
  - [newsletters] – newsletters from a variety of presses and organizations such as the Clements Center for Southwest Studies from SMU, the Texas Outdoor Writers Association and Book News from East Texas Publishers (Box 812, Folder 8)
  - [Texas Book Festival] – newspaper clippings about festival and festival programs and schedule of events from several different festival years (Box 812, Folder 9)
  - Book announcements – announcements of new books, press releases, and other promotional material (3 folders) (Box 812, Folder 10-12)
  - Book catalogs and book lists I – from a variety of publishers, also includes promotional material (3 folders) (Box 812, Folder 13-15)
  - [Invitations to readings, book signings, etc.] – included is a 1998 holiday card from the SWWC/WG, and events such as the Vaquero fundraiser and the Rio Grande panel discussion (Box 813, Folder 1)
  - [Directories and brochures] – a variety of directories and brochures including one to the Wittliff Gallery and for the Daughters of the Republic of Texas library (Box 813, Folder 2)
  - [Book Club of Texas] – variety of material from the Book Club of Texas and the Texas Writers Project, May 1999 (Box 813, Folder 3)
  - [Lone Star Rising] – advance, uncorrected proof of Lone Star Rising by William C. Davis (Box 813, Folder 4)
  - [Newspaper clippings] – numerous newspaper clippings on books, authors and publishing, and includes some material from the internet and magazines (2 folders) (Box 813, Folder 5-6)
  - [Envelope I] – newspaper clippings, Austin Writers League newsletters, and newspaper from Kyle, 1937. Includes letter to Curator Connie Todd (Box 813, Folder 7)
  - [Envelope II] – materials related to Cox's Texana column, newspaper clippings, and drafts. Includes letter to Curator Connie Todd (Box 813, Folder 8)
  - "Texana correspondence" – old correspondence related to Cox's Texana column. Includes letter to Curator Connie Todd (Box 813, Folder 9)
  - "Authors, Texas II" – newspaper clippings and book announcements (2 folders) (Box 813, Folder 10-11)
  - [correspondence, notes and drafts] – this material was no longer in its original file but is made up of various correspondence, some book announcements, hand written and typed notes, and drafts for several pieces by Cox (2 folders) (Box 813, Folder 12-13)
  - [Texas Folklore Society] – newsletters from the Texas Folklore Society, 1990-2001 (Box 813, Folder 14)
  - [Betty Cox – Bob Jamison correspondence] – correspondence, notes, and drafts (2 folders) (Box 813, Folder 15-16)
- Accession 2018-111
  Archival materials following the research of writer, Mike Cox, on the Texas Rangers. This collection is made up of government documents, drafts, stories, Ranger records, obituaries, and biographies of hundreds of former Rangers. The research begins right after the civil war up until the early 2000s.
  - "Rangers 1850s #1"; Notes, Texas State Library, News clippings, Texas State Times, 1855-1859 (Box 2861, Folder 1)
  - "Rangers 1850s #2"; News clippings, Frontier Times, Indians Indians Indians, Report for the Secretary of the Interior, Funeral Info, 1857-1988 (Box 2861, Folder 2)
  - "San Saba Mob"; Dallas Morning News, Austin Daily Statesman, Lonestar Iconocast, 1897-2003 (Box 2861, Folder 3)
  - "Santa Anna/ Coleman E."; The Abilene Morning Reporter News, News clippings, Frontier Times, and Correspondence, 1924-1994 (Box 2861, Folder 4)
  - "Santa Claus bank robbery 12/23/1927"; Invitation, News clippings, Articles, Abilene Reporter News, 1921-2007 (Box 2861, Folder 5)
  - "Rangers – 1830's"; Rules and Regulations, Correspondence, News clippings, Frontier Times, 1843 (Box 2861, Folder 6)
  - "Scott, Capt. M."; News clippings, Genealogy Records, Ancestry.com, August 5, 1882-2004 (Box 2861, Folder 7)
  - "Ramsey, J.A. Murder 1926"; Newspaper Clippings (Box 2861, Folder 8)
  - "Ranger Reunion"; Pamphlet, Texas Ranger Association Foundation, News clippings, 1900-1987 (Box 2861, Folder 9)
  - "Camp Sabinal"; Cavalry Camp Site, and Notes (Box 2861, Folder 10)
  - "Salt War"; Mexican Americans in Texas History, Texas Highways, Voice of the Mexican Border, Frontier Times, 1931-1991 (Box 2861, Folder 11)
  - "San Diego Plan I"; Rebellion in the Borderlands, Newspaper Clippings, 1923 (Box 2861, Folder 12)
  - "Plan of San Diego II"; Texas Historical Commission, Invoices, Correspondence, News clippings, DPS Paperwork, Tom Mayfield, Trail guide (Box 2861, Folder 13)
  - "Warren, Ben C. Killed 2/10/1885"; News clippings, Out of the Past: Cemeteries of West Texas, Ranger Wars Caused by Early Day Fencing (Box 2861, Folder 14)
  - "Ranger Weapons"; Magazine Clippings, Correspondence, Frontier Facts, Invoices, Early Colt Revolvers, Age of the Gun Fighter, The Cattleman (Box 2861, Folder 15)
  - "Williamson, R.M. II/ re:leg 7/00"; Postcard, newspaper clippings, correspondence, 1970-2000 (Box 2861, Folder 16)
  - "Word, Orville T."; DPS papers, Frontier Times (Box 2861, Folder 17)
  - "Wright, 'Dogie'"; Award Ceremony Invitation, Tribute to a Ranger's Lady, Times Herald, 1982-1985 (Box 2861, Folder 18)
  - "Wright, Capt. Will"; The State Trooper, Texas Ranger Dispatch, News clippings, Correspondence, 1899-1942 (Box 2861, Folder 19)
  - "Zimmermann Telegram"; Speaking of Texas, World Journal Tribune, March 1967-January 1994 (Box 2861, Folder 20)
  - "WPA Histories"; Noah Armstrong, Dave Burns, Jesse Jolly, Tom Morgan, Elizabeth Roe, and Daniel Boone Sinclair, 1998 (Box 2861, Folder 21)
  - "Walker's Creek Battle"; Correspondence, William Bollaert's Texas, After San Jacinto, The Boerne Star, Pamphlet, Jack Hay's Big Fight, 1844-2013 (Box 2861, Folder 22)
  - "Wallace, Big Foot"; Newspaper Clippings, The Dawson and Mier Prisoners, Correspondence, American Statesman, Texas Veterans in Mexican War, 1937-1989 (Box 2861, Folder 23)
  - "Ware, Dick"; Colorado City Record, Obituary, Biography, 1902-1997 (Box 2861, Folder 24)
  - "Warnke, Oscar"; News clippings, Notes, April 28, 1979, August 1, 1989 (Box 2861, Folder 25)
  - "Sullivan, John L. Scrapbook"; Photograph, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, Train Tickets, Invoices, Wanted Poster, and Notes (2 folders), 1891-2005 (Box 2862, Folder 1-2)
  - "Tankersly, Fayette"; The Tankersly Family, Ancestry Info, and Notes, 1951 (Box 2862, Folder 3)
  - "Townsend, E.E"; Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, Rangers and Indians in the Big Bend Region, Ranger, River Guard, Ranchman, and Notes, 1923-1999 (Box 2862, Folder 4)
  - "Light Townsend"; Correspondence, News clippings, Sul Ross State Teacher's College Bulletin, 1927-1999 (Box 2862, Folder 5)
  - "Tumlinson"; Correspondence, Mail, Biography, Obituary, DeWitt Colony Militia Captains, 1981-2003 (Box 2862, Folder 6)
  - "Trowbridge, Joe"; Trowbridge Family History, George Trowbridge Murder Trial, 1987 (Box 2862, Folder 7)
  - "Jeff Vaughan"; Jeffrey Eagle Vaughn, Annotated Manuscript, Notes, Correspondence, Warrant of Authority, Oath of Service, The Great Vaughan, 1902-1998 (Box 2862, Folder 8)
  - "Vergara Incident 1914"; News clippings, The Austin Statesman, February–March 1914 (Box 2862, Folder 9)
  - "Samuel Walker"; Notes, Correspondence, Newsletters, Auction Form, Invitations, Mail, True West, Biography, Funeral Literature, and Newspaper Clippings, 1848-2000 (Box 2862, Folder 10)
  - "Fort Sherman"; Fort Sherman in Titus County, Texas, 1964 (Box 2862, Folder 11)
  - "Sherman not 1930"; Dallas Morning News, Austin Statesman, The Houston Press, and Anniversary Speed Graphic, 1930-1990 (Box 2862, Folder 12)
  - "Sowell, A.J."; Early Settlers and Indian Fighters of Southwest Texas, Frontier Times, News clippings, Correspondence, Notes, and Short Stories, 1891-1970 (Box 2862, Folder 13)
  - "Spanish Flu Kills TX Rangers 1918"; "Spanish Flu Kills TX Rangers 1918"; Encyclopedia Americana, Oath of Members Ranger Force, The Influenza Pandemic of 1918, Life at Camp Funston, 1916-1996 (Box 2862, Folder 14)
  - "Silver Stars + Six Guns"; Annotated Manuscripts, Zane Grey Reporter, and Pamphlets, 1987-1990 (Box 2862, Folder 15)
  - "Space Rangers"; Power Rangers in Space, Captain Video and his video Rangers, and articles, 2008 (Box 2862, Folder 16)
  - "Zeno Smith"; Newspaper Clippings, A good man wears a black hat, Notes, DPS papers, and Correspondence, 1945-2012 (Box 2862, Folder 17)
  - "Straight Talk/ FTRA Newsletter"; Newsletters (2 folders), 1994-2005 (Box 2862, Folder 18-19)
  - "TR 2-file; Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, Dallas Morning News, Postcards, Biographies, From Citizen Soldiers to organized police Short Stories (2 folders), 1873-2009 (Box 2862, Folder 20-21)
  - "Seguin Ranger Station"; The Old Ranger Station, Correspondence, Biographies, News clippings, James E. Ivey, 1936-2015 (Box 2862, Folder 22)
  - "Joe Sitters II (Ed Bartholemew File)"; Map, The Long Rio Grande, Short Stories, Interview Transcripts, and Notes, 1896-1991 (Box 2862, Folder 23)
  - "Sterling, W.W."; Clan Sterling Online, The Handbook of Texas Online, 2003 (Box 2862, Folder 24)
  - "Camp San Saba"; Early History of Camp San Saba, Camp San Saba, March 1933 (Box 2862, Folder 25)
  - "Spanish Law Enforcement"; Mission Cattle Rustling, Archivo de la Nacion, Nunca Hemos Sidos rebeldes, 1975-2000 (Box 2862, Folder 26)
  - "Special Rangers"; Texas Ranger Hall of Fame and Museum, The Pittsburgh Gazette, DPS Special Ranger, and Notes, 1935-1986 (Box 2862, Folder 27)